Our super hero's starting to really shape up.
But we have some additional effects you want to make sure we do before we're done with this initial black and white pencil drawing.
And that is first off, there's some of the other things going on in this.
First off, Spiderman, he's suspended in the air.
Where's he's going? He is web slinging which means you have to make sure you have the web sling out. Two lines, drawn straight out, and then basically draw a bunch of spirals the first time through.
Now draw more lines coming out, just like so.
And then I go back here and I draw one more line of spirals at a slightly different angle.
There you go, you have web sling fluid.
Now we also have the other web sling fluid which he's just letting go of.
The skin is letting go of something so we have to make sure we draw that in here.
This is more of web slinging stuff.
Let's put this in here.
It's material that loops around a lot.
It's very dynamic.
So now we basically go back through there and we just kind of scraggle around the edges.
See how I'm kind of like going around like in little spirals all the way around it, all the way to the top?
Now come down in some thick lines, thick tapering lines.
Because this is supposed to be more of a rope like substance.
And there you go, now you have your web slinging fluid back behind there.
The last thing is kind of a bit of a background.
Right now our hero's on a white ocean.
And let's draw in some other lines back in here.
You should show some dynamic flow.
And down around here diagonally kind of show a little more, a little more dynamic, a little more action, just right in here going all across the page.
It makes it a little more interesting.
Let's make it snowing behind him.
So a couple of circles randomly placed, different shapes and sizes all flaking our hero.
And at this point you've completed your friendly neighborhood Spiderman slinging home on a very very cold winter afternoon, perhaps on his way to a family gathering or hopefully someplace else nice and warm and give him a break from fighting all that crime.